herinteractive.com 2018-02-05

# Privacy Policy | Nancy Drew Games | Her Interactive

The following provisions apply to information Her Interactive learns about or obtains from you when you visit the Her Interactive Web site (the “site”). By accessing and/or using the site, you agree to be bound by the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

These provisions may be changed from time to time and without notice, at Her Interactive’s sole discretion and as provided by applicable law. You should check this Privacy Policy frequently for any such changes, but in any case your continued access or use of the site shall constitute acceptance of any modifications of the Privacy Policy. Her Interactive’s use of information gathered or obtained now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such use.

### General

The site is intended to be interesting and useful to visitors of all ages. Her Interactive values the privacy and safety of children (and adults) who may visit the site. If you are under age 13, you must obtain your parent or guardian’s consent before providing any personal information to the site or participating in the Message Board. This Privacy Policy explains what you need to do. If you are a child under age 13 and have questions about these Terms, or anything else on the site, please ask your parent or guardian for help. If you are a parent of guardian of a child under age 13 or are interested in the Site’s policy for collection of personal information from children, please see our [Message to Parents](https://www.herinteractive.com/about-us/for-parents/ "For Parents").

### What We Collect

Information You Give Us: Her Interactive receives and stores any information you enter on the site (for example, when you register with the site or register a warranty, participate in chat or bulletin boards, or participate in contests, events or promotions) or provide in any other manner, including via Email. This may include your personally identifiable information, such as your name, e-mail address, home address, phone number or other personally-identifiable information (“Personal Information”). Her Interactive may also collect general demographic information, such as your age, hobbies, and other preferences. Her Interactive will only collect personal information reasonably necessary to comply with your requests and with Her Interactive’s legitimate business interests. Of course, you can choose not to provide such information, but you might not be able to access certain sections of the site or use certain services. Her Interactive uses the information that you provide for such purposes as facilitating your use of the site, responding to your requests for information, improving the products and services we offer, and communicating with you regarding special events, news, announcements and other topics. In addition, please see our [Message Board Rules](http://community.herinteractive.com/faq.php?faq=rules2#faq_ruleslist) for information on personal information you may disclose in messages you post.

Children Under Age 13: If you are under age 13, Her Interactive must receive your parent or guardian’s consent before you provide any personal information or participate in the Message Board.

Resumes: Your personal information contained in any resume or application for employment you submit to the site will be used solely for the purpose of evaluating you for possible job openings with Her Interactive and/or its affiliates, and for responding to your requests for information regarding such openings.

Automated Information Collection: Like almost all Web sites, Her Interactive receives and stores certain types of information whenever you visit the site. In addition to information you provide, we may collect the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the IP address of the computer you are using; the browser and operating system you are using; the date and time you access the site; and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to the site. We use “cookies” to automatically gather some of this information. A cookie is a small text file that Her Interactive system sends to your computer to collect information about your activities on the site. The cookie transmits this information back to the site each time your browser requests a page from the site, and the information is stored to help facilitate your use of the site the next time you visit. If you do not want to receive cookies from the site, you can set your browser to not accept cookies.

### How We Use Information

We use the information you provide and we collect to:

  * Administer the site and diagnose problems with our server;
  * Verify your identity;
  * Provide you with information about the site and Her Interactive and our products and services; and in order to facilitate performance by Her Interactive or you under any agreement you may enter into with Her Interactive; and
  * Measure the number of visitors to the site and how the site is used, in order to make the site as useful as possible to our visitors.

### Sharing Information

We do not share information collected or obtained from you with any third parties.

### Links

The site may contain links to other sites. These links are for the convenience of visitors to the site only, and Her Interactive makes no representations whatsoever regarding such other sites. You should review the privacy policies of other sites carefully before providing any information to such sites. Her Interactive is not responsible for the privacy policies or procedures or the content of any other site.

### Security

Her Interactive has reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information under Her Interactive’s control. The database server which houses the message board information is behind a firewall and inaccessible from the internet. The firewalls disallow anyone without proper authentication from contacting the server in any way other than HTTP. The password scheme for the message board uses a method of encryption, that has been proven to be a highly secure encryption method.

### Subpoenas

Her Interactive does not disclose the identities of visitors or users of the site unless legally required to do so. We will respond to any subpoena received from a government agency (i.e., the Securities and Exchange Commission or law enforcement agencies) without prior notice to you. Unless prohibited by law or by a valid court order, we will notify you of any subpoena received from any other party (i.e., for civil litigation) which requires us to disclose your identity, and will wait ten (10) days, or a lesser amount of time as required by the deadline in the subpoena, before providing the information requested by the subpoena.

### Opt-Out

If you want your name removed from Her Interactive’s database or to change or modify any of your information collected by Her Interactive, you may do so by:

  * Choosing to “opt-out” prior to submitting any information;
  * Sending an email to [webmaster@herinteractive.com](mailto:webmaster@herinteractive.com)
  * By mail to the following address:

Her Interactive  
Opt-Out  
Her Interactive  
325 – 118th Ave. S.E., Suite 209  
Bellevue, WA 98005

In addition, if you are registered with the site, you may review and/or update your contact information, or request that we remove your information from Her Interactive’s database by the following the second, third or fourth contact option set forth above. Please include your screen name and/or the Email address you used when you registered, so that Her Interactive can verify your request.

### Conditions of Use

Your access and use of the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy, and your use of the Message Board is subject to the Terms and Rules  
View the Rules at [Messageboard Rules](https://www.herinteractive.com/privacy-policy/message-board-policies/ "Message Board Policies")  
View the Terms at [Terms of Use](https://www.herinteractive.com/privacy-policy/terms-of-use/)

### Contacting the Site

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or the site, please contact:

Her Interactive Inc. c/o Privacy  
325 – 118th Ave. S.E., Suite 209  
Bellevue, WA 98005
